talk about hakeem jeffries for a moment who now may face a challenge from tsa who is a member of
the dsa you said that there are local issues that mr osay should be focused on maybe should remain
a councilman are you saying he should not run against hakeem jeffries no i'm saying that i
think the focus should be right here on new york city i respect the work that council member osay
has done what does that mean should he not run i think that right now is not the time to be to be
engaging in that kind of a primary let me just say before i respond to this nonsense that anybody
who wants to come in here and go i told you he was gonna you can fuck off democrats sucking is
not revelatory i guess some of you guys think that's an own because you think it's binary
like you either have to be outside of the electoral system or you have to constantly
kiss the ass and democrats anyway this video is not about arguing with other people on the left
about electoralism versus not it's about this bullshit this is fucking bullshit what kind of
horseshit is this how come no one asked him why because this was the shit that aoc pulled the other
day oh it's not the time why why why isn't it the time can either of you explain why it's not the time
because you know what i think democrats love to tell people it's not the time they love that it
wasn't the time to criticize anybody in the democratic party during trump's first administration
because we had to resist the administration then it wasn't the time to criticize the democratic party
during the primary because we needed to consolidate to beat trump then after biden won it wasn't the
time to criticize them because he needed to get his agenda through of which of course he didn't then it
wasn't the time to criticize them because we needed to keep our powder dry so that he would work with
the progressive so this whole like it's not the time is really just the controlled opposition and
this has been going on since literally slavery and the quote-unquote ally abolitionists right the white
abolitionists who are all about like yes we need slavery to end like it's no bueno we're always saying
but we need you to do it like a certain way you have to be non-violent and let's not like rush things we
just really need to like do this methodically meanwhile black people are enslaved and they're being killed
methodically and this whole not the time not the time is again an aspect of privilege and controlled
opposition that we have seen over and over and over again and now we are seeing it by those who are not
white but are absolutely upper but are absolutely operating within these spaces right so even the
it's not the time was something that was always told to martin luther king and he talks about this
and i'd say this ad nauseum in his book where do we go from here the last book before he was assassinated
and he talks about how liberals are far more dangerous than the racists because they're the
ones who are in the way of progress they will always preserve order before change because they know
that it's going to cause disruption and disruption may mean that they're going to have to lose things they
like by the way i gave zaron the benefit of the doubt when this first came out and he showed you right
damn you shout out to blake lee on the collab
you